Mateusz Stankiewicz

Junior Front-end Developer/Content Editor

A highly motivated and reliable junior front-end developer with a passion for creating websites. Enjoy working as part of a team. Self-started, paying strong attention to detail. Eager to learn and develop knowledge and skills. Currently looking for a new and challenging position within a company where I could grow both personally and professionally. Come back home to Poland after six years spent abroad. Open for remote work.



- mateuszstankiewicz999@gmail.com
- Białystok, Poland
- matthewstanki.github.io
- github.com/matthewstanki

- +48 728034680 (Poland) | +44 7548163066 (England)
- 27 July, 1993
- linkedin.com/in/mateusz-stankiewicz
- (instagram.com/matthewstanki

WORK EXPERIENCE

High reach FLT driver **DMW Logistics**

2016 - 2021

Sutton-in-Ashfield, England

• Loading and unloading materials from a variety of vehicles. Moving pallet-packed materials around the site or storage facility. Performing equipment checks and basic maintenance. Quality checking and counting stocks. Driving high reach FLT.

Warehouse operative / Production worker (temporary work)

Freshstart Recruitment LTD / Senior Salmon Recruitment Agency

2015 - 2016

Nottinghamshire, England

• Work in various fast-paced environments such as Bonds Confectionery, Jigsaw Foods, Synseal Extrusions. Duties include picking and packing orders, loading and unloading goods from lorries, operating production line equipment, cleaning work areas.

EDUCATION

University of Technology Białystok

Front-end Development

2014 - 2015

Białystok, Poland

· Web applications / Frontend Development

Secondary School No.7

Language class

2010 - 2013

Białystok, Poland

English

German

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATES



- Google Analytics for Beginners
- Advanced Google Analytics
- Getting Started with Google Analytics 360
- Google Ads Search
- Google Ads Display

- Introduction to Ableton Live 9
- CSS Positioning
- Bootstrap 4: Getting Started
- Semantic HTML
- Building Websites with HTML
- Web Layouts with Flexbox and Bootstrap 4 • HTML, CSS and JavaScript: The Big Picture
- Enhancing Web UIs with Parallax Scrolling Introduction to CSS
- Creating Responsive Pages with Flexbox CSS

- Writing in Plain English
 AWS Essential Training for Developers JavaScript: Classes PHP with MySQL Essential: The Basics
 - Google Cloud Platform GCP Essential Training for Developers
 - Become a Full-Stack Web Developer (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ES6+, Git, React.js, Node.js, SQL, NoSQL Essential Trainings, DevOps Foundations, Learning RestAPIs, Dev Search Techniques)

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Simple Form in JavaScript (2022)

- https://github.com/matthewstanki/simple_form_js JavaScript Calculator (2022)
- https://github.com/matthewstanki/js_calculator

PHP Order App (2022)

https://github.com/matthewstanki/order_app_php

Portfolio (2020 - Present)

https://matthewstanki.github.io

My Parallax Movie Project (2020 - 2021)

https://my-parallax-movie-project.web.app

My Arsenal Blog (2019 - 2020)

https://arsenal-kanonierzy.web.app

LÓMË Premium Quality Sportswear (2018 - 2020)

http://lome.azurewebsites.net

MatthewStanki99 School Project (2014 - 2015)

https://matthewstanki99.firebaseapp.com

LANGUAGES

Polish

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

English

• C1 Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Football Formula 1 Creating websites Gym

Cryptocurrency Travelling

Books

Video games

Geography

MMA

WW2

Techno

Movies